http://www.processregister.com/about/privacy.asp

We respect the privacy of those who visit our web site and those who become subscribers.
In accordance with this, we have created this policy in order to demonstrate
our privacy commitment to our users:
What this Privacy Policy Covers
This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when
you are on our site, and when you use our services. This policy also covers
our treatment of any personally identifiable information that third parties share with us.
This policy does not apply to the practices of organizations that we do not own or
control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.
Information Collection and Use
We collect personally identifiable information when you register for an account, when
you use our services, and when you visit our pages. We may also receive personally
identifiable information from third parties.
When you register with us, we ask for your name, email address, zip code, occupation,
industry, and personal interests. Once you register with us and sign in to our services, you
are not anonymous to us.
We use this information for three general purposes: to customize the content you see, to
fulfill your requests for certain services, and to contact you about services.
We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your
browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. This
information is not linked to your account and will not be used to identify you.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
We utilize the Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting based on Display Advertising. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Settings.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
We will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when
We have your consent to share the information;
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Terms of Service
FREE Magazine Section
FREE Magazines Section: ProcessRegister offers users the FREE process, energy and greater manufacturing trade magazines through partnership with TradePub.com, a division of NetLine corporation. If you register for services offered in those "Magazine" areas of our portal, personal information you provide is maintained by NetLine in accordance with NetLine's privacy policy.
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences
We give you the ability to edit your Account Information and preferences at any time,
including whether you want us to contact you about new services.
You may request deletion of your account by sending an email to
.
Security
Your Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.
In certain areas we use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.
Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to
its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes
public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your
personal information
Changes to this Privacy Policy
The privacy policy is subject to modification from time to time. If we decide to change
our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what
information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose
it to anyone. Any significant changes to our privacy policy will be announced on our
home page. If you do not agree with the changes in our policy you have the ability to
remove your account information. This can be done by sending email to
.
Questions or Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions complete a feedback form or send an email to
.
ADD YOUR COMPANY for FREE & instantly promote your website & business to industrial buyers.
• Splendid ROI• 3 Million pageviews• Search Optimization• User Testimonials• Live Proof!• Targeted Buyers
©1998 - 2020 ProcessRegister  TERMS OF USE  |  PRIVACY  |  EDIT LISTING  |  CONTACT US  |  LINK TO US
Find: Suppliers By ProductSuppliers By Name/WebsiteProducts
All Keywords
Any KeywordExact Phrase
ALL COUNTRIESAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaArgentinaArmeniaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBelarusBelgiumBermudaBoliviaBrazilBrunei DarussalamBulgariaCameroonCanada    Alberta    British Columbia    Manitoba    New Brunswick    Newfoundland    Northwest Territories    Nova Scotia    Ontario    Prince Edward Island    Quebec    Saskatchewan    YukonChileChinaColombiaCongoCroatia (Local Name: Hrvatska)CyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEstoniaFinlandFranceGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGuatemalaGuineaHaitiHong KongHungaryIcelandIndia    Andaman & Nicobar    Andhra Pradesh    Arunachal Pradesh    Assam    Bihar    Chandigarh    Chattisgarh    Dadra & Nagar Haveli    Daman & Diu    Delhi    Goa    Gujarat    Haryana    Himachal Pradesh    Jammu & Kashmir    Jharkhand    Karnataka    Kerala    Lakshadweep    Madhya Pradesh    Maharashtra    Manipur    Meghalaya    Mizoram    Nagaland    Orissa    Pondicherry    Punjab    Rajasthan    Sikkim    Tamil Nadu    Telangana    Tripura    Uttar Pradesh    Uttarakhand    West BengalIndonesiaIran (Islamic Republic Of)IraqIrelandIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKorea, Republic OfKuwaitLatviaLebanonLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLithuaniaLuxembourgMacedonia, The Former Yugoslav Republic OfMalaysiaMaltaMauritaniaMauritiusMexicoMonacoMoroccoNepalNetherlandsNew ZealandNigeriaNorwayOmanPakistanPanamaPeruPhilippinesPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussian FederationSao Tome And PrincipeSaudi ArabiaScotlandSerbia and Montenegro
SingaporeSlovakia (Slovak Republic)SloveniaSouth AfricaSpainSri LankaSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwanThailandTrinidad And TobagoTunisiaTurkeyUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited States    Alabama (AL)    Alaska (AK)    Arizona (AZ)    Arkansas (AR)    California (CA)    Colorado (CO)    Connecticut (CT)    Delaware (DE)    District of Columbia (DC)    Florida (FL)    Georgia (GA)    Hawaii (HI)    Idaho (ID)    Illinois (IL)    Indiana (IN)    Iowa (IA)    Kansas (KS)    Kentucky (KY)    Louisiana (LA)    Maine (ME)    Maryland (MD)    Massachusetts (MA)    Michigan (MI)    Minnesota (MN)    Mississippi (MS)    Missouri (MO)    Montana (MT)    Nebraska (NE)    Nevada (NV)    New Hampshire (NH)    New Jersey (NJ)    New Mexico (NM)    New York (NY)    North Carolina (NC)    North Dakota (ND)    Ohio (OH)    Oklahoma (OK)    Oregon (OR)    Pennsylvania (PA)    Rhode Island (RI)    South Carolina (SC)    South Dakota (SD)    Tennessee (TN)    Texas (TX)    Utah (UT)    Vermont (VT)    Virginia (VA)    Washington (WA)    West Virginia (WV)    Wisconsin (WI)    Wyoming (WY)UruguayVenezuelaViet NamYemenYugoslaviaZimbabwe
About Us   |   Contact Us   |   Site Map
